

# Eijiro Osaki Full Stack Developer

#### **About Me**

Hello! I'm Eijiro Ozaki. Passionate fullstack developer with 5+ years of experience developing software under both web and mobile environments. Specialty in Node.js, PHP and Python frameworks, as well as React, Angular and Vue on the front-end. Additional experience has been gained in the areas of staff responsibility, hiring, leadership, and project management.

### **Professional Skills**



# **Work Experience**

### Full Stack Developer at PokerPeek

Oct 2020 - Present

Worked for implementing new features to the website and admin panel with new features.

Skills: Vue, React, PostgreSQL, Node.js, GraphQL

### Full Stack Developer at VisionLab GmbH & Co.KG

Apr 2018 - Mar 2020

Managed Web projects related with AR, VR, XMPP, SaaS and desired to make PaaS like Vuforia, QuickBlox.

Skills: React, Vue, PostgreSQL, Node.js, GraphQL

## Back End Developer at VisionLab GmbH & Co.KG

Sep 2016 - Apr 2018

Completed XMPP Chat Service based on web-socket and node.js and Live support with own chat framework.

Skills: MongoDB, Node.js, MySQL, GraphQL, Python

### **Back End Developer at Blockchain Nordic** Nov 2015 - May 2016

Nov 2015 - May 2016

Worked for building Admin Panel & backend API of this platform and built with Python/Django, MongoDB.

Skills: Python, MongoDB, Node.js, MySQL

# Full Stack Developer at Blood & Treasure Aug 2014 - Sep 2015

Attended 4 projects as a backend developer and Project Lead Developer and completed In-house Self-studying service

platform (Frontend & Backend) with Angular, PHP Laravel Framework and PostgreSQL.

Skills: Angular, PHP, PostgreSQL

**Education** 

# Bachelor of Computer Science from Shizuoka University 2007 - 2011

Aritificial Inteligence - NLP, Fuzzy Logic, Neural Network, Image Processing.

**Contact** 

# **Phone** +1 716 406 3383

Email

## diamondeagle812@gmail.com

Skype

live:.cid.927e726a343e8e9c

()